-继续  -好了
- Carry on. - Yes.
既然大家都跟上进度了
Well, now that we're all up to speed,
我想谈谈艾丽西娅
uh, I want to discuss Alicia.
我觉得我们该和她和解
I think we should turn the temperature down with her.
你想邀请她回来吗
Do you want to invite her back?
这么做  我们就会失去里斯·迪普尔的业务
We do that, we lose Reese Dipple's business.
大卫说得对
I'm afraid David's right,
但可以给她我们多出来的
but we could feed her our overflow.
多出来的
Overflow?
你是说多出来的案子吗
You mean overflow cases?
没错  这对我们不造成经济冲击
Yes, it's financially negligible to us,
但能帮到她
but it could help her.
也能避免她成为坎宁的潜在帮手
It could also help neutralize her as a potential pawn for Canning.
而做我们的人
She'll be our pawn instead.
霍华德
Howard?
我在看都有谁在
I'm checking to see who's here.